In the middle of the seventh month, at the third watch of the night,
the gates of hell open wide,
and the Yin energy is at its heaviest.
Do not knock on the ghost doors,
and do not touch the ghost windows.
Don't come any closer!
A face as white as a lotus.
Adjutant Zhang has arrived!
On behalf of Lord Huo, he presents a jade ruyi,
and a pair of South Sea coral screens.
Come, come.
Please, come inside.
Inspector Jiang Siyao of the Phoenix Police Department
presents
a...
a pink skeleton.
This woman is quite something.
On her wedding day, she jinxed
her new husband to death.
She is a well-known demoness in the capital.
This play is about
Lord Wenchang's Precious Teachings Against Lust.
Beneath this makeup and powder
is nothing but dry bones.
Chief Lei,
wouldn't you say so?
Today is my birthday banquet.
I'm honored that Inspector Jiang
graced us with your presence.
It brings light to my humble dwelling.
Forgive me for not greeting you earlier.
Since it's Chief Lei's birthday,
I shall also present a grand gift.
Inspector Jiang,
please take a seat of honor.
Tell me,
what's going on?
Regarding the pile of bones in the suburban corpse pit,
there are new clues.
What clues?
The forensic doctor found
new white powder left on the body.
It smells like
it's suspected to be from the Jiuhe Gang,
the Jianing powder from the rouge shop.
This is the talcum powder used in cosmetics.
Is there a problem?
The Jiuhe Gang covers a hundred miles,
controlling 80% of the cosmetics business.
How could Chief Lei not know?
This is obviously a smuggled fake.
With just this bag of junk,
you want to frame my Jiuhe Gang?
This is going too far.
Inspector Jiang.
Officer Lin's face was smashed.
This is the white powder extracted
from his hair and clothes.
This talcum powder is from
Lin Jinwen's body,
and it's exactly the same as the talcum powder
sold in your Jianing Powder Shop.
You're making a baseless accusation,
saying the stuff on the victim
belongs to my Jiuhe Gang.
Chief Lei,
I know you killed him.
You, a dignified inspector,
dare to slander my Jiuhe Gang for selling fakes and smuggling,
and even pin this unsolved case
on me.
Is there anyone to judge this?
Excuse me.
I am untalented,
but I can identify
the authenticity of this bag of talcum powder,
and give you two a fair
and clear judgment.
How about it?
Where did this silly boy come from?
If there are no objections,
I'll start.
As for flour particles,
when mixed with water, the starch particles will dissolve,
and the gluten protein will become viscous,
which is what we commonly call kneading dough.
But please note,
this bag of powder does not dissolve in water.
According to the results of my experiment,
the main component of this powder is magnesium silicate.
It is insoluble in water,
with a pH of 7.1, hardness of 1, and specific gravity of 2.7.
That is to say,
this is talcum powder.
Just this bag of powder,
do we need your nonsense here?
The most important thing is,
the particle fineness of this powder is 45.
If it's 45,
isn't this a smuggled fake?
Where are you from?
I am
a mining engineer from Xinfeng Stronghold.
My name is Ye Shian.
A bandit?
If I believe a bandit's words,
how can I, Lei,
survive in the underworld in the future?
What about this?
Inspector Jiang,
if you are here to congratulate,
I have good food and drinks to entertain you.
If you are here to make trouble,
ask my brothers in the Jiuhe Gang
if they agree.
Is this the legendary dumdum bullet?
This is no ordinary bullet.
Because of its extremely high cost,
it is very rare in the country
and is usually only used by killers.
Brat,
who exactly are you?
Didn't I just say?
I am the mining engineer from Xinfeng Stronghold.
I don't care who you are.
You're unlucky to dare come to my hell.
Men,
catch him alive.
Here.
You know how to use it, right?
I should.
Go.
Go quickly.
What about you?
Run!
Fine.
After them!
A beautiful face
is but a flesh-covered skeleton.
A gorgeous appearance.
It is a sharp weapon for killing.
What was that floating in the sky just now?
Was it a ghost?
What are you doing in the Lei Mansion?
My Xinfeng Stronghold
lost a few brothers.
I suspect
it's related to the Jiuhe Gang.
Why should I believe you?
What was that sound?
Is it a human or a ghost?
Ningning, where are my reinforcements?
Senior Sister,
that Superintendent Li Chengrui of yours
is definitely not a good guy.
I took your token to ask him for reinforcements.
Guess what?
As soon as he heard it was the Lei Residence,
he refused to send anyone with me.
She called you Senior Sister.
So just now,
she was the one pretending to be the female ghost.
Yes.
Magic tricks.
Magic.
What are you doing?
Little bandit, how do you know so much?
Don't ask me why I know so much.
I know where the problematic bullets
and the talcum powder are.
If you take me to investigate the case,
I'll tell you.
Okay.
Starting today,
I'll make three rules with you.
Okay.
First, follow my orders.
Okay, Senior Sister.
What about the second and third?
Okay, got it.
Tell me when you want to.
This is the place.
How did you find this place?
I followed the trail of
the missing brothers from Xinfeng Stronghold,
and found the Jiuhe Gang.
There was a guy named Boss Wang
acting suspiciously.
I tailed him for three days
before finding this place.
The killer shot from behind
and is left-handed.
Jinwen was murdered while investigating
the pile of bones case in the suburbs of the capital.
Then his body was taken by the killer
to the wedding venue
and thrown down from the second floor.
You can even tell he's left-handed?
Jinwen must have discovered some secret.
What secret did Lin Jinwen
discover that got him silenced?
The powder and bullets are still here.
Hengtong Company.
Isn't this
Uncle Jiang's business?
My dad.